Xiaoyu,
it's been hard for you
all these years.
Honestly,
sometimes
I don't even know how I got through it.
I understand.
Come on,
cheers to victory.
Xiaoyu,
you can't keep living in hatred.
After all, life goes on.
You are still young.
But
I feel like everything has suddenly lost direction.
How are you
with Lin Jiming?
What do you mean?
I'm a woman,
and your best friend.
I can feel
he has a place in your heart.
There's no chance
between him and me.
He's innocent.
No single snowflake is innocent
when an avalanche occurs.
Lin Jiming,
open the door!
I know you're home.
Lin Jiming,
open the door!
You coward!
Do you know what has happened to the Lin Group?
Are you just hiding at home?
I used to like you.
You jerk!
What do you want from me?
Did my brother
tell you about Wen Yishi?
Oh.
No.
My brother
is still hesitant.
It's normal to be hesitant.
I'm here today
to talk about Lin Jiming.
He
is actually quite pitiful.
What do you want to say?
I went to see him last night,
but he didn't see me.
He didn't even open the door.
Chen Fang said
he hadn't been out for many days.
He didn't answer any calls.
What does that have to do with me?
Aren't you his girlfriend?
And
he likes you very much.
He treats you well.
I think you should talk to him.
No one wants to
see him in this situation.
But some things
can only be overcome by oneself.
Don't you think?
So you dare to say
that you have no responsibility
for his current situation?
Actually, life is like snooker.
Sometimes,
mistakes
are the best offense.
Tiantian,
if you dare to mess with the Liu family,
you'll be fired
as our legal counsel today.
As long as I'm the CEO of Lin Group,
she won't
leave.
Then do you dare to say
that you have no responsibility
for his current situation?
I got this
from Chen Fang.
He said
Lin Jiming kept this card
for you as a backup.
Whether to go or not,
whether to persuade or not,
the choice is yours.
I hope I'm not wrong about you.
Tiantian.
Why are you here?
I came to see if you're dead.
If you're not,
look at this.
Everything is here.
Does it still matter?
What do you mean by that?
Look at yourself now.
You look like the garbage
Wen Shiyi used and threw away.
Are you willing to rot here?
Answer me, Lin Jiming.
Or should I call you
Wu Jiming?
What about you?
Are you
Guan Tiantian
or Gu Qingyu?
Have you ever,
even just for a moment,
been genuinely sincere with me?
Or
from the first time we met,
every time you got close,
every glance,
every smile,
was just part of your revenge plan?
What am I, just a pawn in your game?
Ah!
The sun was shining that day,
just like today.
What do you think
we should name our baby?
Wang Yile.
How does that sound?
Hmm.
[That was the last time I felt]
[my future was bright.]
That day, Jiming was cutting vegetables in the kitchen,
humming a song.
He came up with so many names
for our future child.
Names for a boy,
names for a girl.
Finally, he said the name Yueyue.
Yueyue is the best.
As long as we're happy.
Then there was a loud bang.
Ji Ming's scream.
Xiaoyu.
It stopped abruptly.
Heat wave.
After the glass shattered,
I was flipped over onto the ground.
My stomach hurts so much.
When I woke up again, I was in the hospital.
My whole body hurts.
My face was wrapped up.
I instinctively touched my belly.
It was flat.
The doctor said the baby was gone.
Ji Ming just...
They said it was a gas leak.
Accident.
This was not an accident at all.
It was murder.
Wen Shiyi was afraid that Jìmíng would come back
and fight for the property with her own son.
So she wanted us to die.
She ruined everything of mine.
My home.
My child.
My life.
I crawled back from hell alive.
I endured the pain of surgery time and time again.
I became a different person.
not to hear you ask here
if I ever loved.
I did it to make her pay with her life.
Do you understand?
I thought you were my enemy.
I schemed to get close to you,
gain your trust,
even your love.
But then I realized
you weren't my enemy.
In a sense,
we are both victims.
The reason why I'm here today
is that I don't want to see
Lin Jiming I know
become like this.
The evidence is all here.
You can continue to be the trash of Wen Shiyi,
or get up and end all this.
It's up to you.
But I
will continue to fight.
I want to see Su Wei.
She is under criminal detention now.
The case is still in the investigation stage.
You can't see her as you wish.
You should know the rules.
I have accepted Su Wei's defense commission.
I just want to show her a clear path,
an opportunity to reduce her guilt.
If Su Wei is willing to turn into a state witness,
Wen Shiyi can't hide anymore.
Su Wei is a smart girl.
She should leave herself a way out.
Wen Shiyi's ship is about to sink.
She doesn't have to die with her.
Do you think she will speak up?
She will figure it out.
It just takes some time.
Okay.
I see.
Handle it quickly.
Be clean.
Don't make any mistakes.